{
    "id": "2c28ac9dca9b4b8a96e360e4cd492ac2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A bevy of ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "kittens",
                "cars",
                "girls"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d8121bf4832a4408a0d00f92e102d8fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "A litter of ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "calves",
                "puppies",
                "parrots"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57473840a8aa4e10ac91ddd8a795d426"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of the girls ……………………. given a present.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each and every.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1772fbe40b046b3a69a1d3d9c8412f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She accompanied her children ……………………….. the bus stand.",
            "description": "Till and until shows time up to shows distance.",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01a4969c57c14e18883607a4897b32b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The father unlike his sons ……………… hard working.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun father.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9b318f61251490ab8599727859bfd6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He as well as I ……………………. interested in music.",
            "description": "When you connect two subjects with as well as, the verb agrees with the former subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cbb5980a0a847a58457aa08cc0a8595"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had hardly reached the station ……………………… the train left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "soon",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33bff0c0197844678b6b4da40f6c0c51"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t open the packet. Change into passive",
            "description": "We use let to change imperatives into passive.",
            "answers": [
                "Open not the packet",
                "Packet not be opened",
                "Let the packet not be opened"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "124d0a5770ab4d2f809c19e888471b7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Either the teacher or the students ………………………. clean the class room.",
            "description": "When we connect two subjects with either/or, the verb agrees with the second subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "has to",
                "have to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f0e557019824ddaa7e99994274f74fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… begins at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Happiness",
                "Peace",
                "Character",
                "Charity"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2892f07adba348de9798d1cbc7596713"
        },
        {
            "question": "To meet one’s Waterloo is to ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fight hard",
                "surrender",
                "meet one's final defeat",
                "win"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de4745a119b941e9b5283d0fbdea56f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plural of ox is …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "oxes",
                "oxs",
                "oxen",
                "oxens"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fdc9ef0ef29c4cba9411bfcc786630f1"
        }
    ]
}